your guys
I'm in the best autonomy system in the
world right now the best one you can buy
anyway this cost me 70 thousand dollars
super Chris is really good and I don't
know I don't know if I'm gonna sell any
of these Cadillac ct-6 --iz but we
bought us 86 here I am George at SOCOM
and I ride home
in a ct-6 and want supercruise right now
I'm gonna flip you guys around
it's super good like I don't know what
to say oh my god I mean I I don't know
how much to trust this thing I feel like
I trust it too much it's too easy to
trust it is monitoring the way I'm
looking but like I haven't at least get
in the middle lane there's all of time
to correct it so turns blue
during the lane change now let's see if
it'll turn green again supercruise
disengaging this supercruise
unavailable so okay it's really finicky
like here's the dashboard this icon
appears I think I'm still on cruise
control I'm a little confused right now
bonds dots
yo but I'm riding my caddy yo that's
solo G this is the Mike Jones ship man
this girl texted me she's like I I was
like I bought a Cadillac
she I don't know man that happened
yeah but like yeah I know it's a
Cadillac this is weird this is weird
that like but okay while supercruise was
engaged I was super happy now I can't
get it to engage again now it isn't very
good at telling me right here why it
won't engage
I don't know if this is unmapped or this
is just um
I can't see the lanes right now because
like the layer or the Sun yeah y'all I
got this 468 man negotiate no you can
get a good deal if you negotiate I gotta
know about like rebates and but
yeah I had to pay tax 208 why am i I'm
on the wrong camera
so it comes up is like a little icon
when supercruise is ready I don't know
why it's not ready sees my phone in the
frame it has XO it has a driver facing
camera right here
no but like Catholics are not cool like
this is not cool but but the super curse
is cool I don't understand
this is such a dichotomy can i
supercruise by Facebook Seattle Alliance
unavailable now um oh yeah you can
really see the LEDs they're monitoring
me and check out the review merits an
LCD GM got special approval from Mission
for this yet so while super cruise is
engaged it probably is the best system
you could buy but then when it
disengages you know you don't really
know why this car is kind of too easy to
trust - I like I've never seen super
cruise make a mistake which is kind of
bad
just stop here it's light
send us the cabana li so I don't have
any common art we're in here yet we're
gonna go home we're gonna get the Cabana
link yeah we'll definitely share one
absolutely they got some cool stuff on
cam smell but here I am in my Cadillac
with supercruise van so we'll get it to
engage again hopefully when we get to
the 101 which is coming up soon I'm
driving so I was driving for this I will
show you when I go back to to
supercruise it doesn't engage all the
time and it doesn't tell me why it won't
engage bonus is engaged it feels good so
what it's doing is it's fusing the lane
polynomials with the map polynomials if
GM's this is GM supercruise system um so
GM has already deployed maps they made
the maps they contract with a third
party company and they made the map
satellite or no we didn't get a vault oh
this is the only G I'm Carla buying
Cadillac ct-6 gonna be supported by open
pilot yeah you know it was time to buy
something a little nicer we're gonna the
EON is a Toyota and Honda level trot
product but you know the future products
is luxury for a thousand dollars
basically it's apples model right where
a cell phone company you all know it
should have bought an accord I should
not have bought in the court I love my
Cadillac you guys it's car sick let's
so unfortunately it doesn't have any red
light detection which is kind of
disappointing hope I will get that but
yeah it's got three dashi thingies I
gotta go yeah let's go yeah so we're
gonna run open pilot yep we're gonna do
a portable pop out to the city 6b the
highest-end car with open violet
that's the plan yeah so I would say
super cruise right now at least when
it's engaged is quite a bit better than
open palette they're done they have
driver monitoring which we need chef
when it's engaged right OTA updates no
jam can't do OTA updates the only thing
they can attend a update is the map
module which is a little bit of a
disappointment which is an argument to
not buy this car because there are no mo
TI updates but i mean it shows the
direction that all the mainstream things
are gonna go yeah right no this car is
so sweet
all right let's wait till we're on the
101 and then we'll get back on some
super pretty
yeah yeah we bought a CG sex it's the
Ubuntu Linux of this car ubuntu this is
likely like likely this is the list of
blackberry like they're trying no but I
mean jeans I'm working on this for a
while and like it's I don't know why
they don't hype this up I'm because it
is good maybe they're afraid people will
crash I'm not sure how many cars coming
at this size 6 15 employees 6 cars come
work at common AI and you get access to
the company cars including this Cadillac
ct-6 pretty steep I know I didn't buy
the pan or a Bose stereo with an extra
$5,000 we got the cheapest car we could
get supercruise we have to be
responsible with our spending no I can't
it responsibly spend money on
like pop up LCDs in the back and just
call exhibit if we need some of those
what is supercruise missing of any sort
of feedback on why it won't engage it
doesn't tell me anything about that it
only engages on limited access highways
which are basically freeways which are a
little disappointing
I insist
the Tesla one is good turn here bro
Daniel aim bro
I was sake ninja
this thing's got twin-turbo - so go
racetrack next year beast all y'all's
zero to sixty five point two seconds
open pilot on that car is like when they
installed Android on the Windows Phone
yep pretty much kind of what we're going
for
alright is supercruise better than
autopilot in limited access highways yes
I haven't actually I haven't tried the
new autopilot yet I haven't tried the
new model update I hear good things
about the new model update but um we try
to model three on this loop that we test
open pile it on and it was like open
pilot quality it was not I wasn't great
like I saw it make multiple mistakes
I saw it make multiple mistakes on our
drive done which is where open pilot is
as well super cruise I am yet to see
make a single mistake every time it's
been engaged it's been flawless so we're
gonna see right here live on periscope
maybe the super cruise will pick his
dick no so what I want to start doing
one of the big pushes this year is we
can really start to quantify
disengagement numbers we're gonna
quantify the disengagement supercruise
and I want to prove statistically that
we have a better system who is my core
consumer I don't think about that
man we're gonna build the best
self-driving car in the world just
because we can examples of what it
handles so it handles um limited access
highways
so here we are we get on one on one here
let me get over I don't like using these
systems in the right lane in case I got
it correct I have no idea what the
torque limits are on this car auto pilot
stork limit is scary high so I don't
know like autopilot I'm scared to take
my hand very far for the wheel but let's
see if we can make this engage okay so
we're on Oh super Chris super Chris
unavailable no it showed up for half a
second so workers yes we're on and it
does have a good amount of history
which it's pretty good all right guys we
are super cruising boys let's done this
thing is too easy to trust so if I'm the
first supercruise death well
historically I've kidding guys always
pay attention to pay attention I'm ready
to correct unless this thing has some
kind of crazy high torque limited but I
trust the GM wouldn't do that let's sort
of trust the testimony but I trust the
GM would do so got my hand right here
how good is it at stop cars not good I
found it's a CC system to be worse than
open pilots when I test drove the other
one oh look at that traffic um yeah so
open pilot is yeah our target is 0.5
we'll be on par with supercruise how
close open problem supercruise we got a
ways to go a lot of ways we really have
to do two things we have to get new
models working and we have to get maps
well but both are kind of close how good
is it stop car you have bought repeating
hate bombs brah
alright so super cruisers driving
obviously it just yelled at me for not
paying attention
all right this is super pleasant like it
just there's something about it and this
is scary like open pilot feels somewhat
unstable like it's like look at the look
there's no wobble there is ZERO wobbling
steering though right
um
yeah and like things like this like so
you see the elevation changes at least
in the older autopilot it would they
would travel with theirs just doesn't
seem too
because I think they have elevation dips
and they have maps of all the lanes that
they've downloaded so they know which
lane is exactly which it claimed to have
a one meter accurate localization system
oh yeah of course it's not gonna do any
swervy behind a stopped car like open
pilot does sometimes this is better than
oh try to steer it off a bit yeah
disengage it disengaged yeah I touch the
steering wheel it had resistance at
first and then it disengaged that wasn't
bad see now I'm disengaged which I hate
no re-engage yes thank you oh thank you
okay good because someone could tell
okay zero doesn't stop again
no don't if you're not tech savvy comes
not ready for you yet um but yeah no
super cruise is better than open pilot
now do remember that this is on a UH
there's groves $74,000 out the door so
but no we should be better there's no
excuses this is why we bought this car I
was really like you know I'm justifying
you you guys know cheap I am we were
thinking about buying a Chevy Malibu for
like thirty thousand dollars but you
know for an extra for an extra thirty
five we bought this and the reason is so
everybody can see what our benchmark is
everybody in the company could try this
car turn on super cruise to be like this
is where we need to be by the end of the
year
you guys are hearing this before the
company
what up GM if you're out there watching
no I had no excuses yeah I know it's do
you know we should be I'm paying
attention relax car
[Music]
this is good though yeah they're really
we should be this guy it's stop go now
isn't necessarily bad
many timeline on the system will be for
everyone now we gotta make it good first
like this year I want to beat
supercruise it next year I want to beat
autopilot and I have good strategies to
beat them both super Chris we can
actually be like with the stuff we have
planned for this year we can beat
supercruise a little pilot like Ilan
knows all the same strict tricks I do
we're struggling with all the same
problems the you know sir team
contracted with a company to build the
developments lidar I'm hoping zero point
four point seven one of Pinkpop how
smooth is the braking I felt better
I even think the fusion the stock ACC is
better I think open pilots is better
especially in the Prius the hybrid the
hybrid braking is better than this
da but this cars not a hybrid so you
know I mean you can't realize kinda like
comparing apples to oranges
fusion stock ACC is fantastic yeah I
just wish they had any sort of flame
keeper which is kind of a tragedy and
it's now they have this stupid lockout
on their system so we want to ship
forward we got a shape-ups reflash for
for it you guys know I feel Betty PS
reflects super cause I'm paying
attention if I move my head a little bit
it doesn't uh but it's good no this is
like this is good I think we'll do the
same thing if you're not paying
attention will blink the thing this is
this great UI you know our green is
somewhere else
piano luckily I assume you have to see
you disengagement
I am literally yet to see a
disengagement with this thing super
impressed this is where we need to be
how's the 20 1998 does that have like
the level 3 enabled I heard out he
pulled some with like it's not
enabled yeah we need to get we need to
get maps working this is all this is
Maps its maps that makes the system good
do you know GM just bought maps they
contracted him you guys know I want to
make my own Maps I don't wanna make them
available free for everybody by the end
of the year for Vivian's driving over
the open toilet
worth the extra cash to actually buy
this car now would not recommend buying
this car this is not worth the money if
this was any forty or fifty thousand
dollar car I would say it's worth it
well we'll see how the new air mail guy
works see if he does well how the maps
coming pretty well pretty well I know GM
does know lane change assist despite
this car having four corner radars on
flex right so that late change assist is
gimmicky I don't feel like you really
need it like right here sitting in this
traffic this is the killer app and
supercruise really nailed it Hawkeyes
the future is so cool I don't believe
this has anything to do with Cruz I
think this is pure GM well there's a GM
contractor basically what this is is GM
bought a map and a localizer solution
and map to an extent and then they just
use the lanes to fine tune your
horizontal position
you can see this this LED here is for
super cruise
it's called traffic this is the killer
app however my poor traffic's pretty
good open pilot has this little thing
where like swerves a little if you get
too close to a car we gotta fix that
coming to the next model open pilot will
definitely have driver awareness with
the front camera yeah absolutely
it's actually ready shipped at least
front camera recording optional you can
toggle it on ya guys no dis engagements
yeah this is where we need to be
beautiful
right in the center the lane is quality
I'm driving a Cadillac ct-6 with
supercruise I'm stuck in traffic and
it's kind of an okay experience master
MA sure yeah yeah resume by itself I
know uh actually I don't think I've
gotten down to zero I sure hope it
resumes by itself
yeah resume by itself when is open
public into work as well as this
hopefully by the end of the year yeah
sure what's the question I'm driving
without my hands as actually the manual
encourages one hands it my fault in what
hands on my nothing this is the Cadillac
version of hands-free driving and it is
good honestly if you're rich and you've
got money to blow by this car is there a
max time before it asked for input no I
don't believe so and we're going in the
same direction I'm so open file it as a
six minute timer right now we're gonna
do away with that once we have driver
monitoring BOTS eight BOTS this things
using corner radars to for something
over flex right
how much so this car was 68 eight plus
tax license and registration extra but
it is good
and their driver awareness really it
allows me to use my phone
ya know flex rape and I think we're
gonna buy a flex for adapter oh no you
can't use a cloudy API but you can use
whatever code you want yeah right when I
go to the deal if we're gonna say what a
different dealer the only car they had
came with the pan or a $5,000
infotainment extra package which I
didn't want nope you know one on the
pedals is like open file I mean you saw
me do this this morning in the Civic um
it's just not as good well pounds just
not as good we need to be here we'll get
here now some of it may be just the
actuator quality that we're dealing with
but GM has a special night hazel Club
video API come on we can actually ship
that
no my feet aren't on the pedals right
there what 2 foot if GM flips a switch
in this car is this gonna eclipse a p2
dial not even close I don't think Jam
can ot8 us but it is the best system in
the market today
and it just shows it just shows we got a
ways to go thought about we got to do it
we're pushing on it it's gonna happen
you guys are gonna get something
credible by the end of the year 0.5
notice engagements yeah pass Eagles 1 is
fine to train with we don't care
fantasy equals wanted not engaging or
pretty much the same thing but GM with
two super cruise I don't know why they
don't market this stuff more they got
they should ship this on every one of
their cars so
bring up to speed on comedy I google us
they go bow feel better yes I do they do
have 4G LTE but I don't think they can
OTA modules
if only this thing had a usable nav
system I'm confused
reset
get on that road and cut over to the 280
where hopefully there's no traffic oh it
looks like there's actually no traffic
once we get past that point
you believe traffic I know I know it's
kind of brutal paying attention relax
this is too easy to trust as well
oh so Chris is not gonna the head unit
how are we gonna cut in let's say as
flawless
that was flawless good job damn
the centering and non wobble I know what
little red lights
this is commas first flex red card yeah
oh okay all right it could have been
better there it accelerated and late
break for the cutter but not too late
but not to the point that it felt unsafe
just cook down that's neither
it's follow distance is conservative
probably similar to open pilots
the steering feels dead center and it
feels like a wheels not moving like open
pile it just feels like it like sways we
got to get rid of it
you are bought you are glad bad man bad
do you work for the company what company
I worked for Qi I'm no work for coming I
do you like the mirror man will give a
key sight you just followed this with
home but no I don't think you just
follow distance with this either
I don't think you can it's good you
shouldn't be allowed to just follow
business if I press the gas let's say I
just touched it barely let's see if I
can actually press the gas
no it doesn't disengage on gas
it does not decision gas which I don't
agree with
yeah
I don't know maybe we should rethink
that I don't like the idea of letting
the gas be used but
maybe it's okay
I mean no like the problem is up oh wow
okay I mean it could have been Sakai
okay fine you see you guys saw that cut
in
like that's an algorithm issue your
argument for why shouldn't be as make
sense but yeah we just need to be better
am I just a test driver you have a test
driver I'm one of colonised test drivers
then it was George Hotz googleman yeah
yeah super cruisin
why allow the car to drive itself I
don't understand that question but first
engaging your foot should definitely be
allowed to be on the gas that's allowed
I don't know if that doesn't work
professional tennis cover what Avenue
landscape Vivian's out of the car I do
portrait guys on portrait Parrish Cobra
the rearview mirror is green
screen look at that screen throw but
like okay yeah I'm very happy with it
yeah we're doing awareness to her again
this year I'm very happy with Supergirl
I'm waiting for it to mess up I haven't
seen it mess up yet like I see know all
about it messes up all the time
hmm
how do the car know when to change lanes
in the car does not change lanes where
are we closing down the 101
in my Cadillac see you sector
what happens a seat belt unbuckles Trat
stays engaged noobs
yeah it's much stricter engagement but
no I've seen autopilot an old pilot mess
up like here so it always stays in the
middle lane seems whatever Lane you put
it and open the door alright guys I'm on
the highway
this car isn't ready why I'm pretty
happy with it now get into the passenger
seat alright no dumbass what do you
go doing a face recognition they're
recognizing my face
yeah the autopilot is better we got work
to do guys we got work to do
the company meeting when you get back
they're using intel our mobile ID chips
I think it's called life I think there's
a bubble on mobile I combined with they
have a they called the OnStar mapping
module we don't CNN's it's not the
problem like they do this with maps okay
so this is all being done with mapped
areas which is decent strategy the
mirror might be the most underrated
thing in the car the Maris
doesn't it's like open pilot point cloud
a better CNN you're working on that
stuff yeah and I RPG and CD absolutely
guess Oh bow it's about to get a lot
better and now we have a benchmark to
know exactly how much better we have to
make it
I'm not worried about the old Bob
sux their grave do you know where you're
gonna demo your own HD maps see
improvement coming - for sex
um cement so lose jobs supervise love
them super hard yeah be nice quad yeah
notifications
I'm wasting gas how am I wasting gas oh
okay all right little why we're steering
too much steering too much like it's
wobbling this wobbling it's still good
it's still good but not perfect that
wobble
I don't know though I feel like you're
just nipping it this place is way better
how it makes mistakes
I should be steering why
not letting the car to be tough morally
wrong to like cars drive themselves so
we very argument is
their own ways and Castro on the
computer should GM put sanitary watch
chip
supercruise disengaging why why no it
was so good
please reengage I miss my super Cruz
super is unavailable I don't understand
like it was really good and now it's
unavailable why oh okay
the cunning detector only seems to be
good when you have super cruise on bad
now super cruise is not available great
honestly like I wouldn't put it past um
to use a different cotton detector for
their ACC and their super cruise so that
ACC we had a late caught it and if I hit
the brakes I would hit that guy maybe I
would a EB but like and now I can't
engage so I can't engage it comes up a
little thing there
engage come on super cruise come on
super cruise
supercruise not available
crews braking on adaptive cruise set 250
see now I can't turn supercruise on it
now I don't know why open pilot will
always tell you why I wish when I press
the spot it didn't just say unavailable
but their driver transition system is
pretty good it flashes red vibrates you
see
no we should have supercruise level
quality on freeways there's no excuses
guys no excuses
your hand should be on the wheel you
moron I brought your band
turn off ignition to reset that's even
it
this is done a bellboy I don't know why
I'm sure that tells me why on can i Momo
Assam crews in their back on super guru
try looking straight ahead and for a sec
with the phone down call tech support
Louis Jia did I can ask again stick a
panda then we get home
one who's the same dude statistically
Safety's better if it can be enabled
everywhere question of all it's all
questionable who knows
it's ice DGM land yeah Sam you're in on
the joke
what spam I see the spammer
morally wrong hands to be off the old
cars and right
GM encourages hands-free
pull on starman disengages all right yes
alas hey my supercruise disengaged the
car wants me to do things uncomfortable
go back to my supercruise safe space
what trick is morally wrong I agree with
that blink your lights on the steering
wheel it's not German are not blinking
light they're the American made LED up
oh oh my god okay great thanks for not
okay it's cutting detection is on par
with open planets
twin turbo and now I can't engage all
right so it's longitudinals pretty weak
its laterals pretty good backer
supercruise
it's the PWM you know that car didn't
stop when the pilot is the lower
standard yeah guys we're not we're on
par with we're not the best yeah if you
get a CAG oh yeah probably
there's no audible cues no it doesn't
have audible cues but know what you guys
don't realize is it vibrates my seat
it's better than an audible cue it's
good it sounds pretty nice and happy
with the engine
- jab marriage energy merge energy would
be so nice if the car could do merges
for me that'd be so nice can I have
super cruise back no silver cruise Oh
super cruise on the bridge would be so
nice I haven't seen it do any hardcore
curves like I don't think I really can
okay well I don't get any supercruise
here do I know why no clue
it's very painful to have to drive after
supercruise
all right here's the plan guys by the
end of the year I want to release a
video showing a super cruise drive and
an open pilot drive and I want the old
pal job to be better that is where we
need to be
Thank You belt ACC's better
[Music]
boy super creepy we're tired the long
day it took like five hours to get this
car from the dealership
any visual cues yeah that's this style
like bar up top along with a vibration
seat for yellows or Reds
all right come on Cruz back supergirls
let's go
just like I hate that like please tell
me why it doesn't work right now the
little icons not there
yes we bought a Cadillac we did
holiday
we're back
okay so no mistakes but no engage this
is definitely the next model you need
open pilot on we're building open pop
super Chris disengaging bow
oh my phone battery's low thanks car up
now it like reengaged
this like sticky crap on my hands okay I
never mind it's terrible open pilot can
do this now it sees the lanes
crews not available great oh and there's
traffic no I need snow crews do you ever
change lanes down
all right scope ease I think we're gonna
leave you in a little bit let me see if
I can get back on super cruise so I can
wave goodbye come on sir crews let's go
let's go let's go
all right I'll settle for a CC thank you
for joining that was the common AI gets
a Cadillac with some Cruz periscope and
expect to see a lot more of it and Oh
Bob's gonna be better by the end of the
year
all right all right